Sobirjon Bobojonov

Backend developer

18.05.2000 +998997090576 Bukhara, Uzbekistan sobirbobojonov2000@gmail.com

About Me

Backend developer with considerable Django and Django Rest Framework experience. Extensive Python experience (Django +2, Django Rest Framework +2.5) Excellent web professional and developer fluent in several languages, including Python, Django, Django Rest Framework, Postgresql, and others.

• Website:@stackoverflow.com/users/22082174/sobirjon-bol

• LinkedIn@https://www.linkedin.com/in/sobir-bobojonov-9a

Telegram: @StepByStepUp

Instagram: @sobirjon_0576

• GitHub: @BobojonovSobir0576

Work Experience

Backend developer at UniPoint Software Development OOO Full-time	Mar 2023 — Present
Backend developer at Kwork, Freelancer Kwork.uz Part-time	Jan 2022 — Present
Backend developer at General Information LTD, NamSeoul University Korea www.nsu.ac.kr/en/?m1=home Full-time	Dec 2022 — Mar 2023
Backend developer at Bukhara regional administration buxoro.uz Full-time	Jan 2022 — Nov 2022
Backend developer at IT PARK Bukhara regional branch it-park.uz/ru/itpark Full-time	Dec 2020 — Oct 2021
Backend developer at Bukhara regional administration	Feb 2020 — Dec 2020

Education

buxoro.uz

• Asian International University 2019 — 2023

Computer Science and Information Security - Bachelor's degree

Languages

Uzbek - Native
 English - B1 - Intermediate

• Russian - B1 - Intermediate

Full-time

Skills

Python	Django	Django REST Framework (DRF)		Django AllAuth		SQL	PostgreSQL
Microsoft SG	QL Server (MSSQL) WebSocket	MongoDE	3 :	SoapUl	HTML	CSS
Redis	Object-Oriented	d Programming (OOP)	Git	GitHub	Pos	stman	Web Developmer
Web Servers	s Back En	d (Software Engineering)					

Awards

• Full Stack Developer Track

Udacity Proof: View

• Full Stack Developer Track

Udacity Proof: <u>View</u>